{
  "al": {
    "region": "Alabama",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "8tRU",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "NbCY",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Sept. 14"
      },
      {
        "id": "JNLT",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7"
      },
      {
        "id": "fDRt",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Voters need to provide a photo copy of an approved ID with their absentee ballot application. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://www.sos.alabama.gov/alabama-votes/voter/voter-id]"
      },
      {
        "id": "gNBj",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.alabama.gov/alabama-votes/voter/absentee-voting"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "nDER",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "State Board of Education",
        "Commissioner of Agriculture and Industries",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "Public Service Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "DV5E",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/24/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.sos.alabama.gov/sites/default/files/voter-pdfs/nvra-2.pdf?_ga=2.151867641.1776539306.1643579940-1569075100.1643579940",
      "online_link": "https://www.alabamainteractive.org/sos/voter_registration/voterRegistrationWelcome.action",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "ak": {
    "region": "Alaska",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "bgVu",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "5R5Q",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "LsGJ",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "NHJb",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is requested, though some forms of nonphoto ID are also accepted. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot that automatically undergoes additional scrutiny. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://www.elections.alaska.gov/Core/votingatthepollsonelectionday.php]"
      },
      {
        "id": "8PR2",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.elections.alaska.gov/Core/absenteeearlyandinpersonvoting.php"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "sFkK",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "ty4M",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/09/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/09/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/09/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://absenteeballotapplication.alaska.gov/",
      "online_link": "https://voterregistration.alaska.gov/",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "az": {
    "region": "Arizona",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "Z31s",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "96hs",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 12."
      },
      {
        "id": "c7o4",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "ZrtU",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required."
      },
      {
        "id": "wfR3",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.azcleanelections.gov/how-to-vote/early-voting/in-person"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "tBW7",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "Corporation Commission",
        "Mine Inspector",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "LYgW",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/11/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://azsos.gov/sites/default/files/20200417_AZ_Voter_Registration_Form_Printable_0.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://servicearizona.com/VoterRegistration/selectLanguage",
      "change_party_link": "https://servicearizona.com/VoterRegistration/selectLanguage"
    }
  },
  "ar": {
    "region": "Arkansas",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "tLqu",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "Vsh6",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "i1Yq",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "2Qwh",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is required. "
      },
      {
        "id": "VgEh",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.arkansas.gov/elections/voter-information/voter-registration-information/voting-in-arkansas"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "mmc1",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "Public Lands Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "QCvG",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": false,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "N/A",
      "mail_link": "https://www.sos.arkansas.gov/elections/voter-information/voter-registration-information",
      "online_link": "N/A",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "ca": {
    "region": "California",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "jaxx",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available in some counties. "
      },
      {
        "id": "PRVA",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "It varies. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "KLnz",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "It varies. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "Ctna",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required for early voting, except for some first-time voters. More information _here_.[https://www.sos.ca.gov/elections/voter-registration/vote-mail#vote-by-mail]"
      },
      {
        "id": "nWNc",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.ca.gov/elections/voting-info/ways-vote"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "HD8r",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Controller",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "State Board of Equalization",
        "Insurance Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "aLSB",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/24/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://registertovote.ca.gov/",
      "online_link": "https://registertovote.ca.gov/",
      "change_party_link": "https://registertovote.ca.gov/",
      "youth_key": "registerYouth_1"
    }
  },
  "co": {
    "region": "Colorado",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "bs83",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "cy6s",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "wDNx",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "z6i3",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required to vote early. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_. [https://www.sos.state.co.us/pubs/elections/vote/acceptableFormsOfID.html]"
      },
      {
        "id": "xs7Y",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "aTww",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "State Board of Education",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "qWgB",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/31/2022",
      "deadline_online": "11/08/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.sos.state.co.us/pubs/elections/vote/VoterRegFormEnglish.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://www.coloradosos.gov/voter/pages/pub/olvr/verifyNewVoter.xhtml",
      "change_party_link": "https://www.coloradosos.gov/voter/pages/pub/olvr/findVoterReg.xhtml"
    }
  },
  "ct": {
    "region": "Connecticut",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "DB96",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "8PxQ",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "N/A"
      },
      {
        "id": "vPsU",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "yRpW",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. For some first-time voters, ID is required. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_. [https://portal.ct.gov/SOTS/Election-Services/FAQ/FAQ---Voter-Identification]"
      },
      {
        "id": "Y6uL",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://portal.ct.gov/SOTS/Election-Services/Voter-Information/Absentee-Ballot-Process"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "9T3a",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Comptroller",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "s1mZ",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/01/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "11/01/2022",
      "deadline_online": "11/01/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://portal.ct.gov/SOTS/Election-Services/Register-to-Vote/Voter-Registration-Application-English-and-Spanish",
      "online_link": "https://voterregistration.ct.gov/OLVR/welcome.do",
      "change_party_link": "https://voterregistration.ct.gov/OLVR/welcome.do"
    }
  },
  "de": {
    "region": "Delaware",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "M9SE",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "CJyD",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Dates and locations will be posted _here_ at least 30 days before Election Day. [https://elections.delaware.gov/] "
      },
      {
        "id": "uVaS",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Dates and locations will be posted _here_ at least 30 days before Election Day. [https://elections.delaware.gov/]"
      },
      {
        "id": "XvtT",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_. [https://elections.delaware.gov/information/faq/voting.shtml]"
      },
      {
        "id": "DMLh",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "1jMp",
      "answer": [
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "vHhe",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/15/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/15/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/15/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://elections.delaware.gov/voter/votereg.shtml",
      "online_link": "https://ivote.de.gov/VoterView/registrant/newregistrant",
      "change_party_link": "https://ivote.de.gov/VoterView"
    }
  },
  "dc": {
    "region": "District of Columbia",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "Mzvs",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "BDp5",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 24 for in-person absentee, Friday, Oct. 28 for early voting."
      },
      {
        "id": "PKd2",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "Fd8t",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required to vote early, except for first time mail voters. More information _here_.[https://dcboe.org/Voters/How-to-Vote/Mail-Ballot-Instructions]"
      },
      {
        "id": "GmFS",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://earlyvoting.dcboe.org/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "oieX",
      "answer": [
        "Mayor",
        "Attorney General",
        "City Council"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "KeDj",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/19/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/19/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://dcboe.org/Voters/Register-To-Vote/Register-to-Vote",
      "online_link": "https://vr.dcboe.org/213324797239968?agency_code=12",
      "change_party_link": "https://vr.dcboe.org/213324797239968?agency_code=12"
    }
  },
  "fl": {
    "region": "Florida",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "rn1H",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "2cHb",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "No later than Saturday, Oct. 29."
      },
      {
        "id": "U48y",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5, but some counties might extend this until Sunday, Nov. 6."
      },
      {
        "id": "a9GE",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Voters need to provide an ID number when requesting a mail ballot. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://dos.myflorida.com/elections/for-voters/voting/vote-by-mail/]"
      },
      {
        "id": "Mx6f",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://dos.myflorida.com/elections/for-voters/voting/early-voting-and-drop-boxes/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "seqT",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Chief Financial Officer",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "686Z",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/11/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://dos.myflorida.com/elections/for-voters/voter-registration/register-to-vote-or-update-your-information/",
      "online_link": "https://registertovoteflorida.gov/",
      "change_party_link": "https://dos.myflorida.com/elections/for-voters/voter-registration/register-to-vote-or-update-your-information/"
    }
  },
  "ga": {
    "region": "Georgia",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "8oME",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "ByYd",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 17."
      },
      {
        "id": "E85A",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "nKVU",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Voters need to provide their Georgia driver's license number or a photo copy of an approved ID with their absentee ballot application. Valid forms of ID can be found _here_.[https://sos.ga.gov/admin/uploads/2021_Absentee_App.9721_2.pdf]"
      },
      {
        "id": "Mroc",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sos.ga.gov/index.php/Elections/absentee_voting_in_georgia"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "y8Ax",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "Labor Commissioner",
        "Insurance Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "XiTN",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/11/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://sos.ga.gov/how-to-guide/how-guide-registering-vote",
      "online_link": "https://sos.ga.gov/how-to-guide/how-guide-registering-vote",
      "change_party_link": "N/A",
      "youth": "Under 18? You can register to vote at 17 \u00BD and vote at 18.",
      "youth_link": "https://sos.ga.gov/how-to-guide/how-guide-registering-vote",
      "felon": "\"Off Paper\" (formerly incarcerated)? You can vote!",
      "felon_link": "https://gjp.org/voting/",
      "check_link": "https://www.mvp.sos.ga.gov/MVP/mvp.do"
    }
  },
  "hi": {
    "region": "Hawaii",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "Kqir",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "U5uU",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Oct. 25."
      },
      {
        "id": "i23D",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "rAs3",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required."
      },
      {
        "id": "aaP4",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://elections.hawaii.gov/voting/voting-in-hawaii/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "s7hV",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Office of Hawaiian Affairs",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "vdVR",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/31/2022",
      "deadline_online": "11/08/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://elections.hawaii.gov/wp-content/uploads/VR-Form-English-20210614C-Form-Fillable.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://olvr.hawaii.gov/Default.aspx?redir=1",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "id": {
    "region": "Idaho",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "so2V",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available in some counties. "
      },
      {
        "id": "9dSt",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "No later than Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "WoY4",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "rehT",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://voteidaho.gov/identification-requirements/]"
      },
      {
        "id": "AbHU",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "B5cK",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Controller",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "n7ZU",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/14/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/14/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://sos.idaho.gov/elections/forms/voter_registration.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://elections.sos.idaho.gov/ElectionLink/ElectionLink/ApplicationInstructions.aspx",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "il": {
    "region": "Illinois",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "g3mx",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes, early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "gihV",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Sept. 29."
      },
      {
        "id": "jH9k",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "2U3m",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required to vote early. ID is only required when registering to vote."
      },
      {
        "id": "vCRY",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://elections.il.gov/votingandregistrationsystems/beforeelectionday.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "hWe3",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Comptroller",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "oZBH",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/23/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www2.illinois.gov/hfs/SiteCollectionDocuments/sber19.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://ova.elections.il.gov/?Name=eYQq6FDqMBHM6r%2fWhrJ1SIpY4MGJGocO&T=637783653251228213",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "in": {
    "region": "Indiana",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "ZG2F",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "isGm",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 12."
      },
      {
        "id": "QWuQ",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7, 12 p.m."
      },
      {
        "id": "TD4W",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_. [https://www.in.gov/sos/elections/voter-information/photo-id-law/]"
      },
      {
        "id": "5nod",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.in.gov/sos/elections/voter-information/ways-to-vote/absentee-voting/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "6oyu",
      "answer": [
        "Secretary of State",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "HpzD",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/11/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.in.gov/sos/elections/voter-information/register-to-vote/",
      "online_link": "http://www.indianavoters.com/",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "ia": {
    "region": "Iowa",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "sjVP",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "ATDA",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 19."
      },
      {
        "id": "MgnN",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "58HK",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Voters must provide their ID number when requesting an absentee ballot. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://sos.iowa.gov/elections/voterinformation/voterIDfaq.html#17]"
      },
      {
        "id": "jda4",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sos.iowa.gov/elections/electioninfo/absenteeinperson.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "oW3c",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "Secretary of Agriculture",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "ZVgF",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/24/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://sos.iowa.gov/elections/pdf/voteapp.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://mymvd.iowadot.gov/Account/Login?ReturnUrl=%2fVoterRegistration",
      "change_party_link": "https://mymvd.iowadot.gov/Account/Login?ReturnUrl=%2fVoterRegistration"
    }
  },
  "ks": {
    "region": "Kansas",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "WPTX",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "nQQd",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Can start as early as Wednesday, Oct. 19, but no later than Tuesday, Nov. 1. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "FRNh",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "4pLp",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Voters need to provide their Kansas driver's license number or a photo copy of an approved ID with their application for an advanced ballot by mail.  Valid forms of ID can be found _here_.[https://www.kssos.org/forms/elections/AV1.pdf]"
      },
      {
        "id": "NWAJ",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://kcdcinfo.ks.gov/voter-registration-and-advanced-voting"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "CjXE",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "State Board of Education",
        "Insurance Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "igB3",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/18/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.kssos.org/forms/elections/voterregistration.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://www.kdor.ks.gov/apps/voterreg/default.aspx",
      "change_party_link": "https://www.kdor.ks.gov/apps/voterreg/default.aspx"
    }
  },
  "ky": {
    "region": "Kentucky",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "EWyD",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "DDC2",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Nov. 3."
      },
      {
        "id": "neTL",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "G5k6",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a provisional ballot, but must provide valid ID to their county clerk's office at a later date in order for their ballot to be counted. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[ https://elect.ky.gov/Frequently-Asked-Questions/Documents/SB%202%20FAQ.pdf]"
      },
      {
        "id": "Syhy",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://elect.ky.gov/Voters/Pages/Absentee-Voting.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "FFaA",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "hKPe",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/11/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://elect.ky.gov/registertovote/Pages/default.aspx",
      "online_link": "https://vrsws.sos.ky.gov/ovrweb/",
      "change_party_link": "https://vrsws.sos.ky.gov/ovrweb/govoteky"
    }
  },
  "la": {
    "region": "Louisiana",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "mgfk",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "8DvG",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 26."
      },
      {
        "id": "Bb8n",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Dec. 3."
      },
      {
        "id": "sPFW",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_. [https://www.sos.la.gov/ElectionsAndVoting/Vote/VoteOnElectionDay/Pages/default.aspx]"
      },
      {
        "id": "nLHV",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.la.gov/ElectionsAndVoting/Vote/VoteEarly/Pages/default.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "JV5o",
      "answer": [
        "Public Service Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "ZWWF",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/09/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "11/09/2022",
      "deadline_online": "11/19/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.sos.la.gov/ElectionsAndVoting/RegisterToVote/Pages/default.aspx",
      "online_link": "https://www.sos.la.gov/ElectionsAndVoting/Pages/OnlineVoterRegistration.aspx",
      "change_party_link": "https://www.sos.la.gov/ElectionsAndVoting/Pages/OnlineVoterRegistration.aspx"
    }
  },
  "me": {
    "region": "Maine",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "55Ww",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "MrmH",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "No later than Friday, Oct. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "4ari",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Nov. 3."
      },
      {
        "id": "P1aK",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first-time voters. More information _here_.[https://apps.web.maine.gov/cgi-bin/online/AbsenteeBallot/index.pl]"
      },
      {
        "id": "7tWY",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.maine.gov/sos/cec/elec/voter-info/absenteeguide.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "fp6y",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "424R",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": false,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_online": "N/A",
      "mail_link": "https://www.maine.gov/sos/cec/elec/voter-info/voterguide.html",
      "online_link": "N/A",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "md": {
    "region": "Maryland",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "Zt8w",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "SB1J",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Oct. 27."
      },
      {
        "id": "rgmL",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Nov. 3."
      },
      {
        "id": "Dy9y",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required."
      },
      {
        "id": "mWAF",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://elections.maryland.gov/voting/early_voting.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "w31U",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Comptroller",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "Aqqg",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/18/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://elections.maryland.gov/voter_registration/application.html",
      "online_link": "https://voterservices.elections.maryland.gov/OnlineVoterRegistration/InstructionsStep1",
      "change_party_link": "https://voterservices.elections.maryland.gov/OnlineVoterRegistration/InstructionsStep1"
    }
  },
  "ma": {
    "region": "Massachusetts",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "eqbT",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "rsvz",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "133P",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7 at 12 p.m."
      },
      {
        "id": "3QeS",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first-time voters. More information _here_.[https://www.sec.state.ma.us/ele/eleidreq/idrequirementsidx.htm]"
      },
      {
        "id": "A5xh",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sec.state.ma.us/ele/eleabsentee/absidx.htm"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "DFzX",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "Governor's Council",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "r7TF",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/19/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/19/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/19/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.sec.state.ma.us/ele/eleifv/howreg.htm",
      "online_link": "https://www.sec.state.ma.us/ovr",
      "change_party_link": "https://www.sec.state.ma.us/ovr/"
    }
  },
  "mi": {
    "region": "Michigan",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "Gx8X",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "61HW",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Sept. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "QmRM",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "h4et",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_. [https://mvic.sos.state.mi.us/Home/VoteInPerson/#id-required]"
      },
      {
        "id": "5kaq",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://mvic.sos.state.mi.us/Home/VoteAtHome"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "YaEN",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "QbXu",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/24/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.michigan.gov/documents/MIVoterRegistration_97046_7.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://mvic.sos.state.mi.us/RegisterVoter/Index",
      "change_party_link": "https://mvic.sos.state.mi.us/RegisterVoter/Index"
    }
  },
  "mn": {
    "region": "Minnesota",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "hMhv",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "vWgY",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Sept. 23."
      },
      {
        "id": "Pav7",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "fgX2",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required."
      },
      {
        "id": "erm3",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.state.mn.us/elections-voting/other-ways-to-vote/vote-early-in-person/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "CHYV",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Auditor",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "Xgme",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/18/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.sos.state.mn.us/elections-voting/register-to-vote/register-on-paper/",
      "online_link": "https://mnvotes.sos.state.mn.us/VoterRegistration/VoterRegistrationMain.aspx",
      "change_party_link": "https://mnvotes.sos.state.mn.us/VoterRegistration/VoterRegistrationMain.aspx"
    }
  },
  "ms": {
    "region": "Mississippi",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "sehp",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "xcm9",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Sept. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "32fk",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "PpJW",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_. [https://www.sos.ms.gov/content/documents/elections/Mississippi%20Voter%20Information%20Guide%202022.pdf]"
      },
      {
        "id": "vQCa",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.ms.gov/content/documents/elections/Mississippi%20Voter%20Information%20Guide%202022.pdf"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "9DCx",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "nnB2",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": false,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/10/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/10/2022",
      "deadline_online": "N/A",
      "mail_link": "https://www.sos.ms.gov/sites/default/files/election_and_voting/Voter_Registration.pdf",
      "online_link": "N/A",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "mo": {
    "region": "Missouri",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "BDz6",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "FsY4",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Sept. 20."
      },
      {
        "id": "EQtV",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "dZ3q",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://www.sos.mo.gov/elections/goVoteMissouri/howtovote#Absentee]"
      },
      {
        "id": "u7zc",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.mo.gov/elections/goVoteMissouri/howtovote#absentee"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "qMhL",
      "answer": [
        "Auditor",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "VYZw",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/12/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/12/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/12/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.sos.mo.gov/elections/goVoteMissouri/register",
      "online_link": "https://s1.sos.mo.gov/elections/voterregistration/",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "mt": {
    "region": "Montana",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "txpV",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "runS",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "No later than Tuesday, Oct. 11."
      },
      {
        "id": "uM6d",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "r4Jg",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required. ID is only required when registering to vote."
      },
      {
        "id": "FBmh",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sosmt.gov/elections/faq/#absentee-voting"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "KB3N",
      "answer": [
        "Public Service Commissioner",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "ncxp",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": false,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/07/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "N/A",
      "mail_link": "https://sosmt.gov/elections/vote/#1641574992907-9dee3295-aa37",
      "online_link": "N/A",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "ne": {
    "region": "Nebraska",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "n58j",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "9gHN",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Oct. 11."
      },
      {
        "id": "SXhL",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "shtT",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first time voters."
      },
      {
        "id": "kp2M",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sos.nebraska.gov/elections/early-voting"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "MvWd",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "State Board of Education",
        "Public Service Commissioner",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "sVKY",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/28/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/21/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/21/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://sos.nebraska.gov/elections/voter-forms",
      "online_link": "https://www.nebraska.gov/apps-sos-voter-registration/",
      "change_party_link": "https://www.nebraska.gov/apps-sos-voter-registration/"
    }
  },
  "nv": {
    "region": "Nevada",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "Hv6r",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "WT3S",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Oct. 22."
      },
      {
        "id": "2dxJ",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "XZKn",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first time voters. More information _here_.[https://www.nvsos.gov/sos/elections/voters/mail-ballot-voting]"
      },
      {
        "id": "x1Nb",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.nvsos.gov/sos/elections/voters/early-voting-information"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "ekG2",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Controller",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "6GTc",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "11/03/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.nvsos.gov/sos/elections/voters/registering-to-vote",
      "online_link": "https://www.nvsos.gov/SOSVoterServices/start.aspx",
      "change_party_link": "https://www.nvsos.gov/SOSVoterServices/start.aspx"
    }
  },
  "nh": {
    "region": "New Hampshire",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "APfv",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available for those who qualify."
      },
      {
        "id": "t177",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Sunday, Oct. 9."
      },
      {
        "id": "opDX",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "E2ST",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. Unless voter did not provide ID when registering to vote. "
      },
      {
        "id": "TPpn",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "JuUx",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "State Executive Council",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "QFTD",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": false,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/26/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/26/2022",
      "deadline_online": "N/A",
      "mail_link": "https://sos.nh.gov/elections/voters/register-to-vote/",
      "online_link": "N/A",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "nj": {
    "region": "New Jersey",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "uJ4e",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "uRBZ",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Oct. 29."
      },
      {
        "id": "sncq",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "XH9s",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first time voters. "
      },
      {
        "id": "gCy9",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.state.nj.us/state/elections/vote-early-voting.shtml"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "xnNc",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "TGBe",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/18/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://nj.gov/state/elections/voter-registration.shtml#vrf",
      "online_link": "https://nj.gov/state/elections/voter-registration.shtml",
      "change_party_link": "https://www.state.nj.us/state/elections/voter-party-affiliation-declaration.shtml"
    }
  },
  "nm": {
    "region": "New Mexico",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "Ycub",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "US2v",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Oct. 11."
      },
      {
        "id": "UKJm",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "jMTT",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required, except for some first-time voters. More information _here_.[https://www.sos.state.nm.us/voting-and-elections/voting-faqs/voting/]"
      },
      {
        "id": "z4MF",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.state.nm.us/voting-and-elections/voting-faqs/early-voting-in-person/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "pGE5",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "Public Education Commission",
        "Public Lands Commissioner",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "MXZD",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/11/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.sos.state.nm.us/voting-and-elections/voting-faqs/voter-registration/",
      "online_link": "https://portal.sos.state.nm.us/OVR/WebPages/InstructionsStep1.aspx",
      "change_party_link": "https://portal.sos.state.nm.us/OVR/WebPages/InstructionsStep1.aspx"
    }
  },
  "ny": {
    "region": "New York",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "To5Y",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "75Do",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Oct. 29."
      },
      {
        "id": "zQja",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Sunday, Nov. 6."
      },
      {
        "id": "Nc5B",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. No document is required to vote, unless you are a first-time voter and ID was not provided upon registration.  "
      },
      {
        "id": "p5kt",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.elections.ny.gov/VotingAbsentee.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "fRvp",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Comptroller",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "8Xti",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/14/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/14/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/14/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.elections.ny.gov/VotingRegister.html",
      "online_link": "https://voterreg.dmv.ny.gov/MotorVoter/?_ga=2.79059091.647255632.1643335721-1445420242.1642719875",
      "change_party_link": "https://dmv.ny.gov/more-info/electronic-voter-registration-application"
    }
  },
  "nc": {
    "region": "North Carolina",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "43PL",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "vJ8i",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Oct. 20."
      },
      {
        "id": "34nx",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "HMfx",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required when applying for an absentee ballot. More information _here_.[https://www.ncsbe.gov/voting/vote-mail/detailed-instructions-vote-mail#1-request-ballot]"
      },
      {
        "id": "pUcq",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.ncsbe.gov/voting/vote-early-person"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "FGFp",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "jfzW",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/14/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/14/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/14/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.ncsbe.gov/registering/how-register/complete-your-registration-mail",
      "online_link": "https://www.ncdot.gov/dmv/offices-services/online/Pages/voter-registration-application.aspx",
      "change_party_link": "https://www.ncsbe.gov/registering/updating-registration"
    }
  },
  "nd": {
    "region": "North Dakota",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "e4FA",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting and in-person absentee voting are available."
      },
      {
        "id": "ecCq",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies by county, early voting may begin 15 days before the election. Check with your local election office."
      },
      {
        "id": "Bddz",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "hSWr",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. If a voter is not able to provide valid ID, they may cast a ballot that is securely set aside until the individual can provide proper identification. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_. [https://vote.nd.gov/IDRequirements.aspx]"
      },
      {
        "id": "7aYM",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "WQLS",
      "answer": [
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "Public Service Commission",
        "Tax Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "AyFN",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": false,
      "deadline_in_person": "N/A",
      "deadline_mail": "N/A",
      "deadline_online": "N/A",
      "mail_link": "N/A",
      "online_link": "N/A",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "oh": {
    "region": "Ohio",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "gBC1",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "4nJF",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 12."
      },
      {
        "id": "xD3w",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7 at 2 p.m."
      },
      {
        "id": "RGzp",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required when requesting an absentee ballot. More information _here_.[https://www.ohiosos.gov/elections/voters/absentee-voting/]"
      },
      {
        "id": "YcG3",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.ohiosos.gov/elections/voters/toolkit/early-voting/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "K1qK",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "State Board of Education",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "vvnP",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/11/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.ohiosos.gov/publications/#vrf",
      "online_link": "https://olvr.ohiosos.gov/",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "ok": {
    "region": "Oklahoma",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "WUAS",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "GFWj",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Nov. 2."
      },
      {
        "id": "hzT8",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "L9Wi",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID or voter identification card is required. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://oklahoma.gov/elections/voters/proof-of-identity.html]"
      },
      {
        "id": "kfWe",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://oklahoma.gov/elections/voters/early-voting.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "NufK",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Auditor",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "Corporation Commissioner",
        "Insurance Commissioner",
        "Labor Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "gySv",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": false,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/14/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/14/2022",
      "deadline_online": "N/A",
      "mail_link": "https://okvoterportal.okelections.us/Home/RegWizard",
      "online_link": "N/A",
      "change_party_link": "https://okvoterportal.okelections.us/"
    }
  },
  "or": {
    "region": "Oregon",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "58Xn",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "No."
      },
      {
        "id": "wbVH",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "N/A"
      },
      {
        "id": "1Qck",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "N/A"
      },
      {
        "id": "xKu5",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is required when registering to vote. More information _here_.[https://sos.oregon.gov/voting/pages/registration.aspx?lang=en]"
      },
      {
        "id": "ojck",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "Cs46",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Labor Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "H38Y",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/18/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://sos.oregon.gov/elections/Documents/SEL500.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://sos.oregon.gov/voting/pages/registration.aspx?lang=en",
      "change_party_link": "https://sos.oregon.gov/voting/pages/myvote.aspx?lang=en"
    }
  },
  "pa": {
    "region": "Pennsylvania",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "ivPN",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "tRft",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Sept. 19."
      },
      {
        "id": "dmP7",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Nov. 1."
      },
      {
        "id": "qTUG",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required when applying for an absentee ballot. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://www.vote.pa.gov/Voting-in-PA/Pages/Mail-and-Absentee-Ballot.aspx#id-mail]"
      },
      {
        "id": "nCjq",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.vote.pa.gov/Voting-in-PA/Pages/Early-Voting.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "6ZTE",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "uyxo",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/24/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.vote.pa.gov/Resources/Documents/Voter_Registration_Application_English.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://www.pavoterservices.pa.gov/pages/VoterRegistrationApplication.aspx",
      "change_party_link": "https://www.vote.pa.gov/Register-to-Vote/Pages/How-to-Update-Your-Registraton.aspx"
    }
  },
  "ri": {
    "region": "Rhode Island",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "DyyJ",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "MkNM",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 19."
      },
      {
        "id": "EtWw",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 11."
      },
      {
        "id": "M38p",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is required. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a provisional ballot. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_. [https://elections.ri.gov/voting/id.php]"
      },
      {
        "id": "MMHR",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://vote.sos.ri.gov/Voter/PersonVotingPage"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "38Lm",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "s4ax",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/09/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/09/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/09/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://vote.sos.ri.gov/Content/Pdfs/voter_registration_form.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://vote.sos.ri.gov/Home/RegistertoVote?ActiveFlag=1",
      "change_party_link": "https://vote.sos.ri.gov/Home/UpdateVoterRecord?ActiveFlag=0"
    }
  },
  "sc": {
    "region": "South Carolina",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "wPk3",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "gAsp",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Tuesday, Oct. 25"
      },
      {
        "id": "V7Cp",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "MRX8",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is required. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://www.scvotes.gov/node/235]"
      },
      {
        "id": "Fq51",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "RfW3",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "Treasurer",
        "Comptroller",
        "Superintendent of Education",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "DQQZ",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/07/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/09/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.scvotes.gov/sites/default/files/VR%20Blank%20Form.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://info.scvotes.sc.gov/eng/ovr/start.aspx",
      "change_party_link": "NAN/A"
    }
  },
  "sd": {
    "region": "South Dakota",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "hNTe",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "wyXK",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Sept. 23."
      },
      {
        "id": "F2Cn",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "QmCb",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is requested when submitting an absentee ballot application. If ID is not provided, voters can have their application notarized. More information _here_.[https://sdsos.gov/elections-voting/voting/absentee-voting.aspx]"
      },
      {
        "id": "dBGe",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sdsos.gov/elections-voting/voting/absentee-voting.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "mx2w",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "State Auditor",
        "State Treasurer",
        "Public Utilities Commissioner",
        "Commissioner of School and Public Lands",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "zG7i",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": false,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_online": "N/A",
      "mail_link": "https://sdsos.gov/elections-voting/voting/register-to-vote/default.aspx",
      "online_link": "N/A",
      "change_party_link": "https://sdsos.gov/elections-voting/voting/registration-changes.aspx"
    }
  },
  "tn": {
    "region": "Tennessee",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "QDcs",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "WvWV",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 19."
      },
      {
        "id": "AVMs",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Thursday, Nov. 3."
      },
      {
        "id": "vmgF",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required. "
      },
      {
        "id": "Uqhs",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sos.tn.gov/elections/guides/how-to-early-vote-in-person"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "xqFK",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "ZSKx",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/11/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://sos-stage.tnsosgovfiles.com/s3fs-public/division/Elections/document/ss-3010.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://ovr.govote.tn.gov/",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "tx": {
    "region": "Texas",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "DiMQ",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "Ys64",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "MM5X",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Nov. 4."
      },
      {
        "id": "KJHX",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required when applying for an absentee ballot and when returning completed ballot. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://www.votetexas.gov/voting-by-mail/index.html]"
      },
      {
        "id": "WGnS",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.votetexas.gov/faq/early-voting.html"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "FicV",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant Governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Comptroller",
        "Land Office Commissioner",
        "Agriculture Commissioner",
        "Railroad Commissioner",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "cumy",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": false,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/11/2022",
      "deadline_online": "N/A",
      "mail_link": "https://www.votetexas.gov/register/index.html",
      "online_link": "N/A",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "ut": {
    "region": "Utah",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "vd5Q",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "tZvX",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "pRjP",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies. Check with your local election office. "
      },
      {
        "id": "twbN",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required. "
      },
      {
        "id": "LaXc",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "rPMe",
      "answer": [
        "Treasurer",
        "U.S Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "EFkp",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/28/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/28/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://voteinfo.utah.gov/wp-content/uploads/sites/42/2021/06/2021-Voter-Registration-Form-06-01-21-1.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://secure.utah.gov/voterreg/login.html?selection=REGISTER",
      "change_party_link": "https://secure.utah.gov/voterreg/login.html?selection=UPDATE"
    }
  },
  "vt": {
    "region": "Vermont",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "3bze",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "aqPm",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "No later than Monday, Oct. 24."
      },
      {
        "id": "WPmx",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "cPKL",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID not required. "
      },
      {
        "id": "o6nB",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://sos.vermont.gov/elections/voters/early-absentee-voting/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "5Jid",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "Attorney General",
        "State Auditor",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "2tMv",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_online": "11/04/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://outside.vermont.gov/dept/sos/Elections%20Division/voters/voterapplication.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://olvr.vermont.gov/",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "va": {
    "region": "Virginia",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "B4bz",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "zALv",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Sept. 23."
      },
      {
        "id": "jDkZ",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "ZYhh",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is requested. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://www.elections.virginia.gov/media/formswarehouse/voter-id/outreach-materials/documents/Voter-Identification-Chart-Rev-4-28-21.pdf]"
      },
      {
        "id": "XLy8",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.elections.virginia.gov/casting-a-ballot/absentee-voting/"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "PXQT",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "Kwcw",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/17/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/17/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/17/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.elections.virginia.gov/media/formswarehouse/veris-voter-registration/applications/VA-NVRA-1-Voter-Registration-Application-rev-4_1-(1).pdf",
      "online_link": "https://vote.elections.virginia.gov/VoterInformation",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "wa": {
    "region": "Washington",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "uisR",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "17Ct",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Oct. 21."
      },
      {
        "id": "Rakd",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "hjpP",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "No. ID is not required. "
      },
      {
        "id": "LZBs",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://www.sos.wa.gov/elections/faq_vote_by_mail.aspx"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "9a8F",
      "answer": [
        "Secretary of State",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "SPqK",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/08/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/31/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/31/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://www.sos.wa.gov/_assets/elections/vrf_print_2022_english.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://voter.votewa.gov/WhereToVote.aspx",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "wv": {
    "region": "West Virginia",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "mKzs",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. Early voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "BGjX",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Wednesday, Oct. 26."
      },
      {
        "id": "s1Ws",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Saturday, Nov. 5."
      },
      {
        "id": "ftSS",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. ID is required. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a provisional ballot if they sign an affidavit attesting to their identity. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_. [https://sos.wv.gov/elections/Pages/BeReg.aspx]"
      },
      {
        "id": "Dkcd",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "http://www.wvlegislature.gov/wvcode/ChapterEntire.cfm?chap=3&art=3&section=3"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "vAxm",
      "answer": [
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "wD36",
      "election_day": false,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/18/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://sos.wv.gov/FormSearch/Elections/Voter/mail%20in%20voter%20registration%20application.pdf",
      "online_link": "https://ovr.sos.wv.gov/Register/Landing",
      "change_party_link": "https://ovr.sos.wv.gov/Register/Landing#Qualifications"
    }
  },
  "wi": {
    "region": "Wisconsin",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "zmsX",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "qktm",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies by county. "
      },
      {
        "id": "X3i3",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Varies by county. "
      },
      {
        "id": "Z8eT",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is required. Voters who do not present valid ID are allowed to cast a provisional ballot, but must provide valid ID to their municipal clerk at a later date in order for their ballot to be counted. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://myvote.wi.gov/Portals/0/Documents/gab_123is_provisional_voting_information_sheet_20_31072.pdf]"
      },
      {
        "id": "6171",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "https://my.lwv.org/wisconsin/local-absentee-ballot-return-and-early-voting-locations"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "v9ZR",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Lieutenant governor",
        "Attorney General",
        "Secretary of State",
        "State Treasurer",
        "U.S. Senator",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "Kjwi",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": true,
      "deadline_in_person": "11/04/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/18/2022",
      "deadline_online": "10/18/2022",
      "mail_link": "https://elections.wi.gov/forms/el-131-fillable",
      "online_link": "https://myvote.wi.gov/en-us/Voter-Registration",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  },
  "wy": {
    "region": "Wyoming",
    "early_voting_faq": [
      {
        "id": "crr7",
        "question": "Can I vote early (before Election Day) in person?",
        "answer": "Yes. In-person absentee voting is available."
      },
      {
        "id": "mZ3Z",
        "question": "When is the first day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Friday, Sept. 23."
      },
      {
        "id": "22P5",
        "question": "When is the last day I can vote early in person?",
        "answer": "Monday, Nov. 7."
      },
      {
        "id": "LozE",
        "question": "Is there an ID requirement? If so, what is an acceptable form of ID?",
        "answer": "Yes. Photo ID is required. Valid forms of ID are listed _here_.[https://sos.wyo.gov/faqs.aspx?root=ELEC]"
      },
      {
        "id": "Hwf1",
        "question": "Additional information",
        "answer": "N/A"
      }
    ],
    "core_races": {
      "id": "4ShE",
      "answer": [
        "Governor",
        "Secretary of State",
        "State Auditor",
        "State Treasurer",
        "Superintendent of Public Instruction",
        "U.S. House of Representatives"
      ]
    },
    "register": {
      "id": "3Rwt",
      "election_day": true,
      "online": false,
      "deadline_in_person": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_mail": "10/24/2022",
      "deadline_online": "N/A",
      "mail_link": "https://sos.wyo.gov/Forms/Elections/General/VoterRegistrationForm.pdf",
      "online_link": "N/A",
      "change_party_link": "N/A"
    }
  }
}
